

## **ORION KIBRET HAILE**

## **OBJECTIVE**

I am a dedicated, a highly driven web developer who seek a challenging opportunity where i can fully use my skills. besides the undergraduate courses at UoG I am also experienced at web developing techniques and freelancing at upwork for almost a while now.

# **EXPERIENCE**

University of Gondar

2021 - Present

Web-developer

I was really helpful to achieve the goal for building a big studentfor-student community services web platform which are available on the local network of the university with my senior friends as a blogger and front-end designer, which is now becoming a model for other campuses in the country.

Upwork.com

2022 - Present

Front-end web developer

So far i have been freelancing on upwork for a while and for the tasks which have been provided by clients, i fully used my skills alongside with my instructors and completed them impressively which got me a satisfied clients.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Gondar

2020 - present

Computer Engineering
3.62

#### CONTACT

- @ ori777ethio@gmail.com
- **+251970468604**
- Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

# SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- Bootstrap
- React Js
- · Willingness to learn
- Self-confidence
- Collaboration

### **INTERESTS**

- Community services
- Photography and photoshop
- Chess
- Literature
- Music(Jazz-blues)